careersvalley.com 2016-12-31

# Privacy Policy | MirchiBazaar

1.Privacy Policy For Email  
2.Privacy Policy For Website

1.Privacy Policy For Email

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

Why did you receive an email from us?

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("double opt-in") or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

The subscription for newsletters is through double opt in mechanism wherein your id will be accepted only after you confirm your email address by clicking on the confirmation link that would be provided.

How we protect your privacy

We employ security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

Sharing and Usage

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

How can you stop receiving email newsletters from us?

Each email newsletter issue sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, you can use the unsubscribe link either at the top right or at the bottom.

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [support@mirchibazaar.com](mailto:support@mirchibazaar.com) for review.

2.Privacy Policy For Website

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [support@mirchibazaar.com](mailto:support@mirchibazaar.com).

At [www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/) and how it is used.

Sharing and Usage:  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your consent or unless ordered by a court of law. We may share information submitted to us with employees managing this information and assigned service providers (for example, courier delivery services) for purposes of contacting you for serving/delivering products/services based upon your request for products/services.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, [www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
[www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Specific info on statistical analytical cookies:  
This website includes cookies by third party statistical analytical tools like that of google analytics which are used to evaluate visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. We will never use these statistical analytics tools to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information of visitors of this website. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/) send directly to your browsers. They may automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. 

Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see on this website and elsewhere on internet.

[www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers and websites.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.mirchibazaar.com](http://www.mirchibazaar.com/)'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Specific info on Google adwords remarketing:  
This website uses adwords remarketing so that users can be served ads depending upon the previous pages they visited. Visitors can opt out of interest-based ads, including remarketing by visiting ads settings page <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

Below Paragraph Is Not Applicable Now:  
[The application as a part of its core service is committed to keep informed the freshers (India) of latest job openings and placement papers. If you wish to visit the application canvas directly without wanting the news feeds you can remove the offline_access extended permission at any time from your account settings.]

With email extended permission we subscribe your mail address to the applications jobs and placement papers newsletter. Again we respect your email privacy and you can unsubscribe at any time via the link that would be present at the bottom of each newsletter.

For any query regarding privacy policy, please mail to [support@mirchibazaar.com](mailto:support@mirchibazaar.com)
